Contact

nicole.baker26@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nicole-baker-44a673a4 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Critical Care

Nursing

Languages

English

Spanish

Nicole Baker

BSN, RN, CCRN

Indianapolis, Indiana Area

Summary

An experienced critical care registered nurse who is deeply committed to providing quality and compassionate nursing care. A team player who is flexible, attentive, and has the ability to effectively communicate. An energetic leader who is passionate about both the patient experience and team morale.

Experience

Travel Nurse

Travel Nurse: ICU, Cath Lab, ED December 2019 - Present (8 months)

Indiana, United States

CFVMC

2 years

CSICU RN

March 2019 - March 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Cath Lab RN

2018 - December 2019 (1 year)

Orlando Health Intensive Care Nurse 2016 - 2017 (1 year)

Florida Hospital

2 years

Assistant Nurse Manager 2015 - 2016 (1 year)

Registered Nurse 2014 - 2016 (2 years)

Laurelbrook Nursing Home

Registered Nurse 2012 - 2014 (2 years)

Southern Adventist University Cashier 2009 - 2011 (2 years)

Education

Southern Adventist University

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2009 - 2014)

Southern Adventist University

Bachelor's Degree, International/Global Studies · (2009 - 2014)